Guide to the Plimpton Family papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, 1848-1994, undated
  - Subseries I.3: Plimpton, Francis T.P. and Pauline Ames Plimpton, 1906-1994, undated
    The bulk of this subseries includes the correspondence between Francis T.P. Plimpton and Pauline Ames Plimpton. When separated, due to professional or family obligations or the occasional solo trip, they corresponded frequently. Other correspondents include their children, parents and the extended Ames, Pearsons and Plimpton families.
    Also included here is the correspondence they received regarding "Letters in Training" a privately published compilation of the letters George Plimpton wrote to his parents while he was stationed in Italy (1945-1946). Francis and Pauline distributed "Letters in Training" to their friends and family at Christmas 1946.
    Francis's correspondence, somewhat more extensive here than Pauline's, includes correspondence with family, friends and teachers dating from his youth. Pauline's correspondence contains letters regarding her writings about Villa Balbianello, a property on Lake Como, Italy, purchased by her uncle, Butler Ames.
    - Francis and Pauline
      - To and From Francis and Pauline, 1932-1971, (12 Folders) (Box 11, Folder 1 to 12)
      - Ames Family--General, 1916-1950 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Ames, Blanche, 1932-1937, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Davis, Evvie, 1933-1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
        (Mrs. John Paschall Davis)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Pearsons Family, 1939-1956, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Plimpton, Calvin H., 1937-1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Plimpton, Fanny Hastings, 1930-1944 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Plimpton, Francis Taylor Pearsons, Jr., 1976-1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Plimpton, George Ames, 1942-1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Plimpton, George Ames--Letters in Training--Regarding, 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Plimpton, George Arthur, 1909-1935, (2 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 9 to 10)
      - Plimpton, Oakes Ames, 1950-1981 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Plimpton, Sarah, 1958-1979 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Stevenson, Adlai, 1958-1960 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Francis
      - 1906-1916 (1 of 2 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - 1906-1916 (2 of 2 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - 1921-1948 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - 1958-1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Family--General, 1939-1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - "Fan Mail," 1961-1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Reminiscences of, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - United Nations Appointment, 1961, (3 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 7 to 9)
    - Pauline
      - 1949-1994 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Service for Francis, 1983, (2 Folders) (Box 14, Folder 2 to 3)
      - Villa Balbianello, 1990-1992, (2 Folders) (Box 14, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Portrait Collection-- George Arthur Plimpton's
      - Correspondence, 1940-1979, (2 Folders) (Box 14, Folder 6 to 7)
      - Information Pages, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Lists, 1926-1956, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Purchases, 1929-1932, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Photographs--Collection, undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Photographs--From dealers, undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Series II: Writings, 1913-1992, undated
  This small series includes the writings of two generations: An address delivered by Frances Taylor Pearsons Plimpton to the Wellesley Club; addresses by George Plimpton; pieces written by Francis T. P. Plimpton dating from a journal he kept in 1913 while on a trip to Europe to drafts dating to 1972; and notes and drafts of several of Pauline Ames Plimpton's works. The material is arranged alphabetically by creator.
  - Plimpton, Frances Taylor Pearsons
    - Address-- Delivered to Wellesley Club, circa 1890s (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Plimpton, George Arthur
    - Addresses, 1913-1915, 1932, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Memoir--Draft, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Printed, 1926-1928 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Plimpton, Francis Taylor Pearsons
    - General, 1926-1972 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - "Amherst Writing," 1920-1922 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - China, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - China--Journal, 1918-1922 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      (pages 1-49 missing)
    - Europe--Journal, 1913, (3 Folders) (Box 15, Folder 7 to 9)
    - "Law as a Career," 1933 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - "In Personam," 1924, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - "In Praise of Polygamy," 1957, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Verse, 1928-1955, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Plimpton, Pauline Ames
    - China, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - "A Collector's Recollections"--Notes and drafts, 1992, undated, (6 Folders) (Box 16, Folder 4 to 9)
    - "The Human Wisdom of Johnson," 1922 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Notes--General, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - "Orchids at Christmas," 1975 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - The Plimpton Papers, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - A Window on our World--More Plimpton Papers, 1987, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Series III: Financial and Real Estate, 1894-1949
  This series contains correspondence regarding donations and loans made by George Arthur Plimpton, as well as financial and insurance transactions with which he was involved (including the estates of Ginn and Company partner, Osmyn P. Conant, and his wife Louise Royce Conant). Documents related to various properties owned by the Plimpton family can also be found here. The material is arranged alphabetically.
  - Donations and Loans, 1901-1934, (7 Folders) (Box 17, Folder 1 to 7)
  - Donations and Loans--"Bad debts," 1912-1922 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Conant, Osmyn P. and Louise R.--Estate
    - Death of, 1910-1911 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence--Family
      - Barton, Annie J. and Anson, 1910-14, (2 Folders) (Box 17, Folder 10 to 11)
      - Conant, Richard Royce--Guardianship of, 1910-1916, (2 Folders) (Box 17, Folder 12 to 13)
      - Eldred, Katherine, 1910-1916 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence--Legal and Financial
      - Melville, Henry, 1910-1915, (2 Folders) (Box 18, Folder 2 to 3)
      - New York Trust Company, 1911-1916, (3 Folders) (Box 18, Folder 4 to 6)
      - Parkhurst, Lewis, 1911 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Insurance, 1910-1912 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Wills, 1910 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Management of Estate, 1910-1915, (2 Folders) (Box 18, Folder 10 to 11)
  - Personal Finances
    - General, 1921-1935 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Ames Hall Trust, 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Bank of Manhattan, 1928-1933, (2 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 1 to 2)
    - College budget--Francis Plimpton, 1920-1921 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Eckert, John A. and Co. Insurance, 1930-1936, (2 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Highland Park Associates, 1913-1922 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Investments, 1919-1934 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Lingley, Baird and Dixon, 1927-1931 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Lingley, R. T. and Co., 1932-1936 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Mutual Life Insurance Company of New York, 1911-1935 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - New England Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1923-1936 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Plimpton Checks, 1897-1898 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Plimpton Estate--Receipts and Disbursements, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Plimpton Trust, 1894, 1935-1936, (2 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 14 to 15)
    - Taxes, 1929-1936 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Real Estate
    - Fifth Avenue--70, 1903-1913 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Fifth Avenue--1165 1930-1931 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Lewis Farm, 1903-1924 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Lewis Farm--Account, 1934-1936, (2 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 3 to 4)
    - Lewis Farm--Insurance, 1913-1917 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Old Hall Street, Liverpool, UK, 1932-1936, (2 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 6 to 7)
    - Park Avenue--61, 1935-1944 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Walpole Realty Corporation, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Series IV: Personal Documents, Ephemera and Realia, 1692-1995, undated
  This sprawling series contains genealogies, documents and artifacts of many generations of the Plimpton, Pearsons and Ames families. The earliest document, dated 1697, is a prose narrative by Mary Plimpton, detailing her religious conversion. Nearly as ancient is a 1699 New Testament owned by D.K. Pearsons. Less esoteric items--baby shoes, a baby book, daily agendas and personal documents--provide hints of the quotidian Plimpton family life. Caches of school work, herbarium specimens, drawings, youthful compositions, report cards and diplomas reveal the educational accomplishments of several generations. Awards, clippings, and scrapbooks document professional achievements. The material is arranged alphabetically.
  - Clippings and Printed Material
    - General, 1949-1976, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Family Obituaries, 1890s-1950, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Francis T. P. Plimpton, 1957-1982, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 3 to 4)
    - George Ames Plimpton, 1953-1982, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - George Arthur Plimpton, 1927-1942, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - George Arthur Plimpton--Funeral, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Pauline Ames Plimpton, 1926-1978, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - "Plimptoniana"--The American Book Collector, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Early Family Documents and Genealogy
    - "Bermuda Childhood"--Memories of by Lucy Horsfall, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Butler, Benjamin, 1876-1982 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Genealogies
      - Ames-Plimpton, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Plimpton Family, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Plimpton Family--notes and correspondence, 1896-1898, 1970-1973, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Plumpton [sic] Family, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Taylor Family--Genealogy Table, 1859 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Pearsons, D.K--Owner of The New Testament of Our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ, 1699 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Pearsons, W.B.C.--in Holyoke Centennial, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Pearsons, W.B.C.--Proclamation signed by Abraham Lincoln, 1864 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Plimpton, Mary--Testimony of Religious Conversion, 1697 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Plimpton Family--Documents, 1726-1808 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Society of John Plympton Descendants, 1963-1980, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Southside--Medfield--General Bills, 1780 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Starr, Comfort--Documents, 1909 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Taylor, Eldad--Documents, 1761, 1775 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Walpole, town of--1832 Survey, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
      (Photostat)
  - Plimpton, Frances Taylor Pearsons
    - Address Book, circa 1890s (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Agendas, 1892-1896, (2 Folders) (Box 22, Folder 11 to 12)
    - Agendas, 1897-1900 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Baby shoes, circa 1864 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Bookplate, undated (circa 1902) (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Homework and Notes, undated (circa 1870s-1880s) (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Italian Books--Exhibit, 1902 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Wedding and Honeymoon, 1892 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Wellesley College--Herbarium Specimens, 1881-1883, (18 Folders) (Box 325, Folder 1 to 18)
    - Wellesley College--Herbarium Specimens, 1881-1883, (17 Folders) (Box 326, Folder 1 to 17)
    - Wellesley College--Herbarium Specimens, 1881-1883, (17 Folders) (Box 327, Folder 1 to 17)
  - Plimpton, George Arthur, 1870-1979
    - Awards and Honorary Degrees, 1904-1931 (Box 39)
      (rolled)
    - Barnard College--Tribute, 1893 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - School Work--Report Cards, Compositions, Addresses and Speeches, 1870-1876, (2 Folders) (Box 23, Folder 6 to 7)
  - Plimpton, Francis T.P.
    - Youth
      - Childhood and Early Education
        - Baby Book, 1900-1902 (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - Brochures, 1910-1913 (Box 24, Folder 2)
        - Drawings, 1906-1913, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 3 to 4)
        - Postcards--Collected, 1910, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - Scrapbook, 1914-1915 (Box 40)
        - School Work, 1907-1917, undated, (2 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 6 to 7)
        - School Work and Compositions--bound, 1911-1913 (Box 25, Folder 1)
        - Sunday School--Annual Letters of Century Class, 1917 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Phillips Exeter
        - General, 1912-1917 (Box 25, Folder 3)
        - The Exonian, 1915-1917 ( 3 volumes) (Box 41)
        - Monthly, 1915-1917 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Amherst College
        - Centennial Class, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 1)
        - Clippings, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, 1917-1923 (Box 26, Folder 3)
        - Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1921 (Box 26, Folder 4)
        - Ephemera 1904-1924 (Box 26, Folder 5)
        - Printed Material, 1917-1922 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Harvard Law School, 1923-1925, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Professional and Vocational Pursuits
      - Academic
        - Amherst College Alumni, 1923-1981, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
        - Phillips Exeter, 1944-1975, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Associations and Awards, 1947-1977, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Associations and Awards--Academic,1936-1983 undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Biographical Sketches--Master File, 1961-1976 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Debevoise, Plimpton, Lyons & Gates--40th Anniversary, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Honors and Diplomas
        - Awards--General, 1922-1966 (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - Awards and Certificates, 1916-1923 (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - Awards and Honorary Degrees, 1952-1981 (Box 38, Folder 3)
        - Certificates--from Mayor of NYC, 1976-1980 (Box 38, Folder 4)
        - Diplomas, 1917-1925 (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - Posters--of talks, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - Rolled--Honorary Degrees, 1952-1981 (Box 39)
      - Scrapbooks of Professional Life
        - 1963-1973, (3 Folders); (unbound) (Box 28, Folder 1 to 3)
        - United Nations, 1961-1965, (bound) (Box 45)
      - General
        - Death, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 4)
        - Death--Memorial Lectures, 1985-1987 (Box 28, Folder 5)
        - Ephemera, 1926-1980, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - George Ames Plimpton
    - Report Cards, 1932-1945 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - School Work, 1943, undated (4 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 8 to 10)
    - Testing--Aptitude, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      (includes Francis T. P. Plimpton, Jr.)
      (restricted until 2021)
  - Pauline Ames Plimpton
    - Diploma, 1918 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Entertaining
      - Guest Books, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Guest Lists, 1957-1982, (2 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 4 to 5)
      - Recipes, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Reading--The Divine Comedy, 1932 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    (heavily annotated)
- Series V: Photographs and Images, circa 1870s-1990s, undated
  Included in this series are individual photographs, negatives and albums of the creators of this collection, their ancestors, their descendants, their properties, and their friends and associates. Material is arranged alphabetically.
  - Subseries V.1: Albums, circa late 1800s-1983
    The albums, some of which were disbound due to preservation concerns, range from a collection of photographs of the Pearsons or Plimpton family dating from the late 1800s to a travel album dated 1982-1983. Included here are albums featuring Francis Plimpton from his childhood through his professional life as an attorney, and at the United Nations. The earliest travel albums are collections of photographs of a trip to Constantinople (1914) and to China (1920). Later photo albums contain pictures of Pauline, Francis, their family and friends on their travels around the world.
    - Plimpton, Francis
      - Childhood, circa 1901-1906, (bound) (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - "Constantinople, Trip to," 1914, (bound) (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Birthday, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Debevoise, Plimpton, Lyons and Gates, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - La Guardia Medal of Honor, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - United Nations, 1960, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - 1961-1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - 1963-1973, (2 Folders) (Box 30, Folder 6 to 7)
    - Plimpton, Francis and Pauline
      - "China," 1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - "Family Album," 1968-1970 (bound) (Box 42)
      - "Sicily, Ausable, West Hills," 1982-1983, (2 Folders) (Box 30, Folder 9 to 10)
      - "Trip Around the World," 1966, (3 Folders) (Box 31, Folder 1 to 3)
      - 1960-1973, (2 Folders) (Box 31, Folder 4 to 5)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - 1974-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 31, Folder 7 to 8)
      - 1975-1980, (2 Folders) (Box 32, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Plimpton, Frances and George Arthur--Pearsons or Plimpton Family Album, circa late 1800s, (bound) (Box 43)
    - Plimpton, George Arthur--"Far East," 1920, (bound) (Box 44)
  - Subseries V.2: Photographs and Negatives, circa 1870s-1980s
    Found here are photographs of the extended Plimpton, Pearsons and Ames families. Especially numerous are the photographs of Francis T.P. Plimpton, which include baby photos, high school and college pictures, photos of Plimpton with his fellow Amherst College trustees, and many pictures of him at work: practicing law, working at the United Nations, and socializing at diplomatic events. Pictures of Pauline Ames Plimpton include portraits and candid photographs with Francis and with their children and extended family.
    - Plimpton, Frances Taylor Pearsons and George Arthur and Extended Family, circa 1870s-circa 1990s
      - Plimpton, Frances Taylor Pearsons
        - 1884-1900s, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
        - Friends, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
        - Grandparents, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
        - Pearsons, W. B. C., Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
        - With George Arthur Plimpton, circa 1890s (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Plimpton, George Arthur
        - Circa 1870s-1930s (Box 33, Folder 6)
        - General, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
        - Portraits, 1920s-1930 (Box 38, Folder 9)
        - Family
          - Adams Family, 1893-1896, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
            (cousins)
          - Gay, Rev. Ebenezer, 1885 (Box 33, Folder 9)
          - Kendall Family, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
          - Plimpton, Calvin G., undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
            (father)
          - Plimpton, Calvin H., circa 1930s-1940s (Box 33, Folder 12)
            (son)
        - Groups
          (including George Arthur Plimpton)
          - Family, 1890s-1930s, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
          - Amherst College Class of 1876, undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
          - Brothers, undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
          - Travel, undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
        - Property and Real Estate
          - General, 1902-1911, undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
          - General--Plimptonville, circa 1918, undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
          - Home--Interior, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
            (41 East 33rd Street, NY, NY)
          - Lewis Farm, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
          - Lewis Farm, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Plimpton, Francis T. P.
      - Youth
        - Baby, 1900-1903, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - Childhood and Adolescence, 1904-1921, undated, (4 Folders) (Box 34, Folder 2 to 5)
        - Exeter--Classmates, circa 1917 (Box 34, Folder 6)
        - Groups--General, circa 1920s (Box 34, Folder 7)
        - Groups--School, circa 1915-1924 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Adulthood
        - General--Oversize
          - Harvard University Law School Reunions, 1965-1980 (Box 37, Folder 8)
          - Sketches and Photographs, circa 1960s-1980, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
          - United Nations--Photographs, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
          - Portraits, circa 1910-1950s, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
          - Portrait--FTPP, PAP and children, 1937 (Box 38, Folder 8)
        - Amherst College--Groups and Events, 1949-1974, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
        - Autographed Photos, 1978-1986, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
          (presidents and NYC mayors)
        - Birthday--80th, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 3)
        - Debevoise and Plimpton--40th Anniversary Dinner, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 4)
        - Family
          - General, 1960s-1990s (Box 35, Folder 5)
          - Francis T.P. Plimpton, Jr., undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
          - George Ames Plimpton, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
          - Pauline Ames Plimpton
            - 1980s undated, (2 Folders) (Box 35, Folder 8 to 9)
            - with Francis, circa 1960s-1980s (Box 35, Folder 10)
            - A Collector's Recollection photos, 1993 (circa 1890-1930s) (Box 35, Folder 11)
        - Honorary Degrees and Awards, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 35, Folder 12)
        - Kendall, Henry Plimpton--Room at University of South Carolina, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
        - Portraits and Bust, circa 1920-1970s (Box 35, Folder 14)
        - Professional and Vocational, 1954-circa 1980s, (3 Folders) (Box 35, Folder 15 to 17)
        - United Nations, circa 1960s (Box 35, Folder 18)
        - Villa Balbianello, undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Negatives, circa 1910-circa 1980s
      - General, 1910s-1920s (12 envelopes) (Box 36, Folder 1 to 12)
      - "China, Trip to," 1920 (36 envelopes) (Box 36, Folder 13 to 48)
      - "A Collector’s Recollections," undated (8 envelopes) (Box 36, Folder 49 to 56)
      - Plimpton, Francis T.P., Portrait, circa 1930s (Box 36, Folder 57)
      - Plimpton, Francis T.P. and Plimpton, Pauline Ames, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 36, Folder 58)
  - Subseries V.3: Special Format Photographs and Images, undated
    These images appear in several formats, including glass slides, daguerreotypes, and one autochrome diascope image of an unidentified sitter, and one silhouette of an unidentified man.
    - Autochrome diascope, undated (Box 46)
    - Daguerreotypes, undated (2) (Box 47)
    - Daguerreotypes--Pearsons, Hannah, circa 1880s--small Box--fragile--framed (2) (Box 47)
    - Slides, Glass--Horn Books and Manuscripts, undated (46) (Box 48)
    - Silhouette, undated (Box 47)